Guide to the Mabou Mines Archive, 1966-2000 (bulk 1970-1995) MSS.133
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Photographs, 146394
  - Subseries A: Production photographs, 146426
    - Starcock Massimo Agus; print, contact sheet, undated; 146466 (Box 28, Folder 1151)
    - Starcock David Dessel; print, undated; 146465 (Box 28, Folder 1152)
    - Sueños Lisa Stein; contact sheets, undated; 146464 (Box 28, Folder 1153)
    - Sueños Lisa Stein; prints; American Repertory Theatre, 1988; 146463 (Box 28, Folder 1154)
    - Sueños Peter Schweizer; contact sheets, negatives for reprint; American Repertory Theatre, 1988; 146462 (Box 28, Folder 1155)
    - Sueños Peter Schweizer; prints; American Repertory Theatre, 1988; 146461 (Box 28, Folder 1156)
    - Sueños Carol Rosegg; prints; Saez and Milián; Triplex Theatre; Feb, 1989; 146460 (Box 28, Folder 1157)
    - Sueños Carol Rosegg; prints; Feb, undated; 146459 (Box 28, Folder 1158)
    - Sueños Peter Schweizer; print; Milián and Smith; Triplex Theatre; Feb, 1989; 146458 (Box 29, Folder 1159)
    - Sueños Carol Rosegg; print; chorus; Triplex Theatre; Feb, 1989; 146457 (Box 29, Folder 1160)
    - Sueños Carol Rosegg; contact sheets; Triplex Theatre; Feb, 1989; 146456 (Box 29, Folder 1161)
    - Sueños Jonathan Atkin; contact sheets, negative; "New York Times"; March, 1989; 146455 (Box 29, Folder 1162)
    - Through the Leaves Nancy Campbell; prints; Interart Theater, 1984; 146454 (Box 29, Folder 1163a)
    - Through the Leaves Donna Gray; print, contact negatives, [1984]; 236424 (Box 29, Folder 1163b)
    - Through the Leaves Gerry Goodstein; print, [1984]; 146453 (Box 29, Folder 1164)
    - Through the Leaves Joseph Schuyler; prints, 1990; 146452 (Box 29, Folder 1165)
    - Through the Leaves prints, [1984]; 146451 (Box 29, Folder 1166)
    - Through the Leaves Nancy Campbell, Joseph Schuyler; contact sheets, negatives, undated; 146450 (Box 29, Folder 1167)
    - Vanishing Pictures Craig Massey, Stephanie Rudolph, undated; 146449 (Box 29, Folder 1168)
    - Worstward Ho Robin Holland; contact sheets, 1986; 146448 (Box 29, Folder 1169)
    - Worstward Ho JoAnn Baker; contact sheets, negatives, undated; 146447 (Box 29, Folder 1170)
    - Worstward Ho Dona Ann McAdams; prints, negatives, undated; 146446 (Box 29, Folder 1171)
    - Worstward Ho prints (snapshots), undated; 146445 (Box 29, Folder 1172)
    - Worstward Ho negative, undated; 146444 (Box 29, Folder 1173)
    - Wrong Guys Craig Massey; prints, contact sheets, undated; 146443 (Box 29, Folder 1174)
    - Wrong Guys Craig Massey; prints, negatives, 1981; 146442 (Box 29, Folder 1175)
    - Wrong Guys Carol Rosegg; prints, negatives, 1981; 146441 (Box 29, Folder 1176)
    - Wrong Guys Carol Rosegg; prints, negative, undated; 146440 (Box 29, Folder 1177)
    - Wrong Guys Carol Rosegg; print, negative, undated; 146439 (Box 29, Folder 1178)
    - Wrong Guys Carol Rosegg; contact sheets, undated; 146438 (Box 29, Folder 1179)
    - Wrong Guys Nancy Campbell; print, negative, contact sheets, 1981; 146437 (Box 29, Folder 1180)
    - Wrong Guys Ilaria Freccia; print, contact sheet, [1981]; 146436 (Box 29, Folder 1181)
    - Wrong Guys contact sheet, undated; 146435 (Box 29, Folder 1182)
    - Wrong Guys Ilaria Freccia; publicity still, [1981]; 146434 (Box 29, Folder 1183)
    - Wrong Guys Ilaria Freccia; publicity stills, [1981]; 146433 (Box 29, Folder 1184)
    - Wrong Guys Ilaria Freccia; publicity stills, [1981]; 146432 (Box 29, Folder 1185)
    - Wrong Guys Ilaria Freccia; publicity stills, [1981]; 146431 (Box 29, Folder 1186)
    - Wrong Guys Ilaria Freccia; publicity stills, [1981]; 146430 (Box 29, Folder 1187)
    - Wrong Guys Ilaria Freccia; publicity stills, [1981]; 146429 (Box 29, Folder 1188)
    - Wrong Guys Ilaria Freccia; publicity stills, [1981]; 146428 (Box 29, Folder 1189)
    - Wrong Guys publicity still, [1981]; 146427 (Box 29, Folder 1190)
  - Subseries B: Company and miscellaneous photographs, 146395
    Mabou Mines company photographs, photos of anniversary events, cast members' head shots, and documentary photographs of Mabou Mines-affiliated productions, photo and slide (see Series V) inventory. All major Mabou Mines members (Akalaitis, Breuer, Maleczech, Neumann, Raymond, Warrilow, etc.) are represented by head shots.
    - Company photos Amnon Ben Nomis; prints, contact sheets, negatives; group shot, 1990; 146425 (Box 30, Folder 1191)
    - Company photos Nancy Campbell; print, contact sheets; group shot, 1984; 146424 (Box 30, Folder 1192)
    - Company photos Paula Court; prints, negatives, contact sheets; [includes photos of Joseph Papp, David Byrne, et al.]; 15th Anniversary Benefit, 1985; 146423 (Box 30, Folder 1193)
    - Company photos Joseph Schuyler; contact sheet; The First 20 Years, Grey Art Gallery, 1990; 146422 (Box 30, Folder 1194)
    - Head shots print; Ellen McElduff, undated; 146421 (Box 30, Folder 1195)
    - Head shots print, negative; JoAnne Akalaitis, undated; 146420 (Box 30, Folder 1196)
    - Head shots prints, contact sheets; Bill Raymond, undated; 146419 (Box 30, Folder 1197)
    - Head shots print; Terry O'Reilly, undated; 146418 (Box 30, Folder 1198)
    - Head shots passport photos; Honora Fergusson, Sabrina Hamilton, undated; 146417 (Box 30, Folder 1199)
    - Head shots print, passport photo; Frederick Neumann, undated; 146416 (Box 30, Folder 1200)
    - Head shots prints, negative; Lee Breuer, undated; 146415 (Box 30, Folder 1201)
    - Head shots print, negative; Lee Breuer, undated; 146414 (Box 30, Folder 1202)
    - Head shots Amnon Ben Nomis; print, negative; Lee Breuer, undated; 146413 (Box 30, Folder 1203)
    - Head shots prints; Ruth Maleczech, two poses, undated; 146412 (Box 30, Folder 1204)
    - Head shots Craig Massey; print, negative; David Warrilow, undated; 146411 (Box 30, Folder 1205)
    - Head shots prints; Lear, George Street cast, undated; 146410 (Box 30, Folder 1206)
    - Head shots Roger Pic, Editions de Minuit; prints; Samuel Beckett, undated; 146409 (Box 30, Folder 1207)
    - Head shots print; Drew Minter, undated; 146408 (Box 30, Folder 1208)
    - Head shots print; Jeffrey Morreau, undated; 146407 (Box 30, Folder 1209)
    - Head shots photocopy; Ron Vawter and Greg Mehrten, undated; 146406 (Box 30, Folder 1210)
    - Head shots print; unidentified actor, undated; 146405 (Box 30, Folder 1211)
    - Miscellaneous photos Ricky McKay; prints; Re-Cher-Chez, 1982; 146404 (Box 30, Folder 1212)
    - Miscellaneous photos Craig Massey; print, negative; David Warrilow, "A Piece of Monologue", undated; 146403 (Box 30, Folder 1213)
    - Miscellaneous photos prints; "Waiting for Godot"; Kent State Univeristy, undated; 146402 (Box 30, Folder 1214)
    - Miscellaneous photos prints; Kent State Univeristy, Fine and Performing Arts Center, undated; 146401 (Box 30, Folder 1215)
    - Miscellaneous photos Ann W. Arlen; contact sheets, letter; Lee and Bill workshop, 1976; 146400 (Box 30, Folder 1216)
    - Miscellaneous photos Martha Swope; print; "Red and Blue," dir. JoAnne Akalaitis, undated; 146399 (Box 30, Folder 1217)
    - Miscellaneous photos unidentified snapshots, undated; 146398 (Box 30, Folder 1218)
    - Miscellaneous photos unidentified personal negatives, undated; 152135 (Box 137)
    - Inventory photo and press inventory as of August 1984, 146397 (Box 30, Folder 1219)
    - Inventory photo and slide inventory, November 10, 2002, 146396 (Box 30, Folder 1220)
- Series V: Slides, 146351
  Series V comprises several hundred slides, some documentary, some actual production elements. The slides were originally housed in either plastic sleeves grouped in three-ring binders, or plastic or cardboard slide boxes. The original labeling on these housings was faithfully transcribed.
  - Subseries A: Documentary slides, 146371
    Slides of documentary photographs of Mabou Mines productions.
    - The B. Beaver Animation, July 1973, 146393 (Box 32, Folder 1225)
    - The Bribe, undated; 146392 (Box 32, Folder 1226)
    - Cold Harbor photographer: Georgina Bedrosian; San Francisco tour photos, 1987, 1987, undated; 146391 (Box 32, Folder 1227)
    - Dead End Kids, undated; 146390 (Box 32, Folder 1228)
    - Dressed Like an Egg etc. photographer: Ken Kobland, June 1977, 1977, undated; 146389 (Box 32, Folder 1229)
    - Flow My Tears, the Policeman Said photographers include: Anne E. Militello; Martha Swope Associates/Carol Rosegg; Jeff Thiebauth, undated; 146388 (Box 32, Folder 1230)
    - Hajj, undated; 146387 (Box 32, Folder 1231)
    - Help Wanted, undated; 146386 (Box 32, Folder 1232)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine photographers include: Andre Grossmann, May 1984; others June 1984-Nov 1985, 1984-5; 146385 (Box 32, Folder 1233)
    - It's a Man's World photographer: George Mott; New York, NY, June, 1987, 146384 (Box 32, Folder 1234)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice photographers include: Amnon B. Nomis, May 1986, 1979, 1986; 146383 (Box 32, Folder 1235)
    - Pretty Boy photographer: Nancy Campbell, March 1984, 146382 (Box 32, Folder 1236)
    - The Red Horse Animation some Jan 1971, 146381 (Box 32, Folder 1237)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation photographers include: Ken Kobland, March 1978; Robin Thomas, 146380 (Box 32, Folder 1238)
    - The Saint and the Football Players July 1973, 146379 (Box 32, Folder 1239)
    - Sueños, undated; 146378 (Box 32, Folder 1240)
    - Through the Leaves Interart Theatre, March-May 1984, 146377 (Box 32, Folder 1241)
    - Through the Leaves April 1986, 146376 (Box 32, Folder 1242)
    - Through the Leaves photographer: Joseph Schuyler, Sept 1990, 146375 (Box 32, Folder 1243)
    - Vanishing Pictures photographer: Ilaria Freccia, [1980]; 146374 (Box 32, Folder 1244)
    - Worstward Ho photographer: JoAnn Baker, 1986; 146373 (Box 32, Folder 1245)
    - ...The First 20 Years photographer: Joseph Schuyler; Grey Art Gallery, 1990; 146372 (Box 32, Folder 1246)
  - Subseries B: Production slides, 146352
    Slides used as production elements in various Mabou Mines productions.
    - Cold Harbor, undated; 146370 (Box 33, Folder 1247)
    - Cold Harbor spare slides, rehearsal 1, undated; 146369 (Box 33, Folder 1248)
    - Cold Harbor spare slides, rehearsal 2, undated; 146368 (Box 33, Folder 1249)
    - Cold Harbor spare slides, rehearsal 3, undated; 146367 (Box 33, Folder 1250)
    - Dead End Kids, undated; 146366 (Box 33, Folder 1251)
    - Flow My Tears, the Policeman Said, undated; 146365 (Box 33, Folder 1252)
    - It's a Man's World, undated; 146364 (Box 33, Folder 1253)
    - Mercier and Camier "ST RUTH LEFT", undated; 146363 (Box 33, Folder 1254)
    - Mercier and Camier "TRAIN RIGHT BOTTOM"; Bill Longcore photos, undated; 146362 (Box 33, Folder 1255)
    - Mercier and Camier "TRAIN RIGHT TOP", undated; 146361 (Box 33, Folder 1256)
    - Mercier and Camier "TRAIN LEFT BOTTOM", undated; 146360 (Box 33, Folder 1257)
    - Mercier and Camier David Warrilow, undated; 146359 (Box 33, Folder 1258)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice beach scene, undated; 146358 (Box 33, Folder 1259)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation dog pictures, undated; 146357 (Box 33, Folder 1260)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation "damaged or need cleaning", undated; 146356 (Box 33, Folder 1261)
    - Starcock, undated; 146355 (Box 33, Folder 1262)
    - Sueños A-I: dictator's maps; J-M1: research slides, undated; 146354 (Box 33, Folder 1263)
    - miscellaneous unidentified production slides, undated; 146353 (Box 33, Folder 1264)
- Series VI: Scripts, 146232
  Scripts, drafts, notes, film treatments, and screenplays representing a majority of Mabou Mines' productions, and some Mabou Mines-affiliated productions. Of particular interest are the many drafts and early versions of Lee Breuer's works, scripts notated by Ruth Maleczech, and a monologue written by Samuel Beckett for David Warrilow.
  Boxes stored offsite: Box 34 - Barcode: 31142042235948 Box 35 - Barcode: 31142042235955 Box 36 - Barcode: 31142042235963 Box 136 - Barcode: 31142042236219
  - The B. Beaver Animation Lee Breuer, undated; 146350 (Box 34, Folder 1265)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042235948
  - The B. Beaver Animation Lee Breuer in "Big Deal," 4 (Fall 1976), 146349 (Box 34, Folder 1266)
  - The B. Beaver Animation Lee Breuer in "Animations: A Trilogy for Mabou Mines" (New York: Performing Arts Journal Publications), 1979; 146348 (Box 34, Folder 1267)
  - The Bribe Terry O'Reilly radio script, undated; 146347 (Box 34, Folder 1268)
  - Cacodemon King Bernard Chartreux, undated; 146346 (Box 34, Folder 1269)
  - Cascando Samuel Beckett (New York: Grove Press, Inc.), [1968]; 146345 (Box 34, Folder 1270)
  - C.E.O. Stig Larsson, trans. Joe Martin, 1989; 146344 (Box 34, Folder 1271)
  - Cold Harbor Dale Worsley, undated; 146343 (Box 34, Folder 1272)
  - Cold Harbor Dale Worsley "Ruth's acting script"; with slide list, copy of Sabrina's notes, undated; 146342 (Box 34, Folder 1273)
  - Cold Harbor Dale Worsley Ruth's script and notes; Aug/Sept 1985, 146341 (Box 34, Folder 1274)
  - Cold Harbor Dale Worsley with notes, index cards, undated; 146340 (Box 34, Folder 1275)
  - Cold Harbor Dale Worsley "Richard Meyer - Elecs. info", undated; 146339 (Box 34, Folder 1276)
  - Cold Harbor Dale Worsley Spanish trans. Antonia Cano; March 1987, 146338 (Box 34, Folder 1277)
  - Cold Harbor Dale Worsley Spanish trans. Adriana Restrepo; May 15, 1987, 146337 (Box 34, Folder 1278)
  - Cold Harbor Dale Worsley "most up-to-date version"; July 1987, 146336 (Box 34, Folder 1279)
  - Cold Harbor Dale Worsley film treatment, version A; May 1988, 146335 (Box 34, Folder 1280)
  - Cold Harbor Dale Worsley film treatment, version B; June 1988, 146334 (Box 34, Folder 1281)
  - Cold Harbor Dale Worsley film treatment, version C; Oct 1988, 146333 (Box 34, Folder 1282)
  - Cold Harbor Dale Worsley screenplay, version A; Feb 2 1989, 146332 (Box 34, Folder 1283)
  - Cold Harbor Dale Worsley Spanish trans., undated; 146331 (Box 34, Folder 1284)
  - Cold Harbor Dale Worsley "Tom Glynn's notation of C.H. blocking incomplete", undated; 146330 (Box 34, Folder 1285)
  - Come and Go Samuel Beckett original script, 1971; 146329 (Box 34, Folder 1286)
  - Company Samuel Beckett photocopies include signed title page, Beckett letter; Oct 1980, 146328 (Box 34, Folder 1287)
  - Dead End Kids JoAnne Akalaitis, undated; 146327 (Box 34, Folder 1288)
  - Dead End Kids JoAnne Akalaitis screenplay, version A; July 24, 1980, 146326 (Box 34, Folder 1289)
  - Dead End Kids JoAnne Akalaitis screenplay; Aug 11, 1982, 146325 (Box 34, Folder 1290)
  - Dead End Kids JoAnne Akalaitis screenplay, draft 1; April 20, 1982, 146324 (Box 34, Folder 1291)
  - Dead End Kids JoAnne Akalaitis screenplay, undated; 146323 (Box 34, Folder 1292)
  - Dressed Like an Egg JoAnne Akalaitis original copy, 1977; 146322 (Box 34, Folder 1293)
  - Dressed Like an Egg JoAnne Akalaitis from "Theater"; Spring 1978, 146321 (Box 34, Folder 1294)
  - Dressed Like an Egg JoAnne Akalaitis Robin Thomas's copy; Sept 12, 1977, 146320 (Box 34, Folder 1295)
  - Dressed Like an Egg JoAnne Akalaitis JoAnne Akalaitis's copy; Sept 12, 1977, 146319 (Box 34, Folder 1296)
  - Easy Daisy Dale Worsley radio play; rejected title: "Birth of a Hippo"; with "Comfort Cage" script, 1980; 146318 (Box 34, Folder 1297)
  - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Philip K. Dick, Linda Hartinian Boston and NY workshop, undated; 146317 (Box 34, Folder 1298)
  - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Philip K. Dick, Linda Hartinian, 1984; 146316 (Box 34, Folder 1299)
  - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Philip K. Dick, Linda Hartinian video script, undated; 146315 (Box 34, Folder 1300)
  - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Philip K. Dick, Linda Hartinian early version, undated; 146314 (Box 34, Folder 1301)
  - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Philip K. Dick, Linda Hartinian "don't use", 1985; 146313 (Box 34, Folder 1302)
  - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Philip K. Dick, Linda Hartinian "don't use"; "not correct"; June 15, 1987, 146312 (Box 34, Folder 1303)
  - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Philip K. Dick, Linda Hartinian "not most recent"; Sept 15, 1987, 146311 (Box 34, Folder 1304)
  - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Philip K. Dick, Linda Hartinian "not quite correct"; May 19, 1988, 146310 (Box 34, Folder 1305)
  - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Philip K. Dick, Linda Hartinian "most recent updated version of script"; Nov 8, 1988, 146309 (Box 34, Folder 1306)
  - Help Wanted Franz Xaver Kroetz, trans. Gitta Honegger, 1984; 146308 (Box 35, Folder 1307)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042235955
  - In the Jungle of Cities Bertolt Brecht, trans. Gerhard Nellhaus with production files, 1991; 146307 (Box 35, Folder 1308)
  - In the Jungle of Cities Bertolt Brecht, trans. Gerhard Nellhaus, undated; 146306 (Box 35, Folder 1309)
  - The Insectiad Lee Breuer, undated; 146305 (Box 35, Folder 1310)
  - The Insectiad Lee Breuer Jan 27, 1992, 146304 (Box 35, Folder 1311)
  - The Insectiad Lee Breuer Feb 26, 1992, 146303 (Box 35, Folder 1312)
  - The Insectiad Lee Breuer, undated; 146302 (Box 35, Folder 1313)
  - The Insect Who Loved the World Lee Breuer, undated; 146301 (Box 35, Folder 1314)
  - Isabelle Eberhardt Mark Rappaport rough assembly for reading; Oct 31, 1988, 146300 (Box 35, Folder 1315)
  - It's a Man's World Greg Mehrten no script: notes, cues, undated; 146299 (Box 35, Folder 1316)
  - It's a Man's World Greg Mehrten, 1985; 146298 (Box 35, Folder 1317)
  - It's a Man's World Greg Mehrten first draft with note to Ruth; April 1985, 146297 (Box 35, Folder 1318)
  - It's a Man's World Greg Mehrten video tech script; June 1987, 146296 (Box 35, Folder 1319)
  - It's a Man's World Greg Mehrten "original for xerox only", 1986; 146295 (Box 35, Folder 1320)
  - It's a Man's World Greg Mehrten performance version; Sept 30, 1985, 146294 (Box 35, Folder 1321)
  - It's a Man's World Greg Mehrten revised; Dec 1986, 146293 (Box 35, Folder 1322)
  - It's a Man's World Greg Mehrten original rehearsal script with letter from Richard Schmiechen, 1985; 146292 (Box 35, Folder 1323)
  - The Joey Schmerda Story James Strahs radio script, undated; 146291 (Box 35, Folder 1324)
  - Love Scenes from Romeo and Juliet adapted by Ruth Maleczech, undated; 146290 (Box 35, Folder 1325)
  - The MahabharANTa Lee Breuer with notes, undated; 146289 (Box 35, Folder 1326)
  - The MahabharANTa Lee Breuer, undated; 146288 (Box 35, Folder 1327)
  - The MahabharANTa Lee Breuer with notes, undated; 146287 (Box 35, Folder 1328)
  - Make a Movie with Mabou Mines, undated; 146286 (Box 35, Folder 1329)
  - Mercier and Camier Samuel Beckett, Frederick Neumann version B; Feb 14, 1979, undated; 146285 (Box 35, Folder 1330)
  - Phaedra Jean Racine, trans. Robert Lowell, undated; 146284 (Box 35, Folder 1331)
  - A Piece of Monologue Samuel Beckett written for David Warrilow, 1979; 146283 (Box 35, Folder 1332)
  - A Prelude to Death in Venice Lee Breuer published in "Plays in Process", 1979-1980; 146282 (Box 35, Folder 1333)
  - Pretty Boy Greg Mehrten, undated; 146281 (Box 35, Folder 1334)
  - Pretty Boy Greg Mehrten final version; June 18, 1984, 146280 (Box 35, Folder 1335)
  - Pretty Boy Greg Mehrten master script, 1984; 146279 (Box 35, Folder 1336)
  - Putana Moksha Leslie Mohn, [1996?]; 146278 (Box 35, Folder 1337)
  - The Quantum Lee Breuer, undated; 146277 (Box 35, Folder 1338)
  - The Quantum Lee Breuer "from Grey [Art Gallery] Reading"; Jan 7, 1991, 146276 (Box 35, Folder 1339)
  - The Quantum Lee Breuer notes, 1990; 146275 (Box 35, Folder 1340)
  - Reel to Real Frederick Neumann draft; Aug 26, 1993, 146274 (Box 36, Folder 1341)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042235963
  - Reel to Real Frederick Neumann incomplete draft IV; Sept 16, 1993, 146273 (Box 36, Folder 1342)
  - Reel to Real Frederick Neumann incomplete draft V; Jan 26, 1994, 146272 (Box 36, Folder 1343)
  - Reel to Real Frederick Neumann film (parts 1-4): samples of script, 1993; 146271 (Box 36, Folder 1344)
  - Reel to Real Frederick Neumann Ruth's script, undated; 146270 (Box 36, Folder 1345)
  - Reel to Real Frederick Neumann excerpt with score; from Al Kryszak, undated; 146269 (Box 36, Folder 1346)
  - Rose… A Dog's Life Lee Breuer, undated; 146268 (Box 36, Folder 1347)
  - Rose… A Dog's Life Lee Breuer notes, undated; 146267 (Box 36, Folder 1348)
  - Rose… A Dog's Life Lee Breuer treatment, undated; 146266 (Box 36, Folder 1349)
  - Rose… A Dog's Life Lee Breuer screenplay, undated; 146265 (Box 36, Folder 1350)
  - Rose… A Dog's Life Lee Breuer excerpts, undated; 146264 (Box 36, Folder 1351)
  - Rose… A Dog's Life Lee Breuer drafts; with "Sister Suzie Cinema", 1992; 146263 (Box 36, Folder 1352)
  - Send/Receive/Send Keith Sonnier, undated; 146262 (Box 36, Folder 1353)
  - Sister Suzie Cinema Lee Breuer, Bob Telson libretto and Lee's intro; published in "Theater"; Summer 1981, 146261 (Box 36, Folder 1354)
  - Southern Exposure JoAnne Akalaitis, undated; 146260 (Box 36, Folder 1355)
  - Starcock Apple Vail, undated; 146259 (Box 36, Folder 1356)
  - Sueños Herschel Garfein, Ruth Maleczech score, undated; 146258 (Box 36, Folder 1357)
  - Sueños Herschel Garfein, Ruth Maleczech score for Hasty Pudding, Cambridge, MA; April 2, 1988, 146257 (Box 36, Folder 1358)
  - Sueños Herschel Garfein, Ruth Maleczech score for Hasty Pudding, Cambridge, MA; April 2, 1988, 146256 (Box 36, Folder 1359)
  - Sueños Herschel Garfein, Ruth Maleczech piano/vocal score, 1987; 146255 (Box 36, Folder 1360)
  - Sueños Ruth Maleczech, 1988; 146254 (Box 36, Folder 1361)
  - Sueños Ruth Maleczech early version, 1988; 146253 (Box 36, Folder 1362)
  - Termite Lee Breuer notes, undated; 146252 (Box 36, Folder 1363)
  - Through the Leaves Franz Xaver Kroetz, trans. Roger Downey, 1983; 146251 (Box 36, Folder 1364)
  - Through the Leaves Franz Xaver Kroetz, trans. Roger Downey German script with translator's synopsis, 1982; 146250 (Box 36, Folder 1365)
  - Through the Leaves Franz Xaver Kroetz, trans. Roger Downey rehearsal script; Women's Interart Theatre; March 1984, 146249 (Box 36, Folder 1366)
  - Viktor Frankenstein Terry O'Reilly drafts, 1991; 146248 (Box 36, Folder 1367)
  - The Warrior Ant Lee Breuer early version, undated; 146247 (Box 36, Folder 1368)
  - The Warrior Ant Lee Breuer, undated; 146246 (Box 36, Folder 1369)
  - The Warrior Ant Lee Breuer "undated very early version 1987 and earlier", 146245 (Box 36, Folder 1370)
  - The Warrior Ant Lee Breuer early version, 1984, 1986; 146244 (Box 36, Folder 1371)
  - The Warrior Ant Lee Breuer excerpts; "The Quantum", undated; 146243 (Box 36, Folder 1372)
  - The Warrior Ant Lee Breuer "From An Ant in Hell: The Warrior Ant, Part Four"; 1987, 146242 (Box 36, Folder 1373)
  - The Warrior Ant Lee Breuer, undated; 146241 (Box 36, Folder 1374)
  - The Warrior Ant Lee Breuer, undated; 146240 (Box 36, Folder 1375)
  - The Warrior Ant Lee Breuer original, 1990; 146239 (Box 36, Folder 1376)
  - The Warrior Ant Lee Breuer early version with pages from "An Epidog", undated; 146238 (Box 36, Folder 1377)
  - Where the Señoritas Are Janis Astor del Valle, 1993; 146237 (Box 36, Folder 1378)
  - Worstward Ho Samuel Beckett, 1983; 146236 (Box 36, Folder 1379)
  - Worstward Ho Samuel Beckett "1st SM SCRIPT (NOT FOR USE)", undated; 146235 (Box 36, Folder 1380)
  - Worstward Ho Samuel Beckett "FINAL S.M. SCRIPT", undated; 146234 (Box 36, Folder 1381)
  - Wrong Guys James Strahs version B; Sept 14, 1981, 146233 (Box 36, Folder 1382)
  - Misc. and unsolicited scripts, 1989-1996; 152131 (Box 136)
    Stücke (1989) by Franz Xaver Kroetz; Angel (1989) by Mayo Simon; Cabin Fever (1990) by Jack Boyle; K-Mille (1991) by Aden Ross; Irene, Goodnight (1993) by Kate M. Esposito; Party on Avenue B (1994) by John Campo; Granny's Formula (1995) and In God I Trust... (1994) by Sam Sherman; Kiss the Babies Goodbye (1996) by Marilyn Livingston
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042236219
- Series VII: Production Books, 146155